myshopkart.net 2007-12-14

# My Shop Kart

Privacy Notice

Effective **01/01/06**

 **Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**  

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the myshopkart.net website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Billing Information  

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order  for webosting only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your webhosting account via the logins you were provided when you setup your account. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information via your site admin area. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please use the contact link <http://www.myshopkart.net/contact_us.php> in order to let us know. 

Copyright Mikkema International Inc. All Rights Reserved.   
email: [support@myshopkart.net](mailto:support@myshopkart.net)
